(Leonard:)And you know that deep down inside,
Howard's a really nice guy.
(Penny:)The problem isn't what's on the inside.
It's the creepy candy coating.
(Leonard:)Will you at least think about it?
Just as a favor to me?
[SIGHS]
The great thing about Ernie
was he never asked me for anything.
(Penny:)He just gave.
(Sheldon:)Got it. Got it. Got it.
Betty and Veronica. Oh.
(Stuart:)Hey, Sheldon, the new Green Lantern
figurine's coming in tomorrow.
(Stuart:)-Want me to set one aside for you?
-Thank you.
(Sheldon:)You just robbed me of the opportunity
to stumble upon the figurine...
(Sheldon:)...and make the oh-so-satisfying journey
from discovery to desire to possession.
(Stuart:)-All right, I won't.
-But I must have it.
(Stuart:)-Okay, I'll set one aside for you.
-Thank you.
(Sheldon:)I can buy all these things online.
I come here for the personal service.